Register of the Fritz Machlup Papers, 1911-1983
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1911-1983.
  - "Credit Facilities or Reserve Allotments?" Banca Nazionale del Lavoro Quarterly Review, 1967 June. Printed copy (Folder 10)
  - "The Efficiency of Partial Devaluations of the Dollar," 1967 July 11. Speech, Cleveland, Ohio. Notes (Folder 11)
  - "International Monetary Reform: Present Positions and the Chances for Agreement," 1967 July 13. Notes for a speech (Folder 12)
  - "Oligopoly and the Free Society," Antitrust Law and Economics Review, 1967 July/August. Typescript of German translation and correspondence with Horst Demmler (Folder 13)
  - "Theoretical Problems: The Phillips Curve," 1967 August 17. Paper, Ulricehamn Conference on Incomes Policy, Studieforbundet Naringsliv och Samhalle, Stockholm, Sweden. Notes and holograph. Includes paper by Erik Lundberg (Folder 14)
  - "From Dormant Liabilities to Dormant Assets," The Banker, 1967 September. Printed copy and review (Folder 15)
  - "Corporate Management, National Interest, and Behavioral Theory," Journal of Political Economy, 1967 October. Partial typescript (Folder 16)
  - "Strong Dollar Seen in Free Markets" (with William J. Fellner, Milton Friedman, and Harry G. Johnson), 1967 November 22. Letter to the editor, New York Times. Printed copy (Folder 17)
  - Notes for speeches on the international monetary system, ca. 1968 (in German) (Folder 18)
  - "Patents," in David L. Sills, ed., International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1968. Typescript (Folder 19)
  - Remaking the International Monetary System: The Rio Agreement and Beyond, 1968
    - Reviews (Folder 20)
    - Comments and correspondence (Folder 21)
  - "Sonderziehungsrechte, Dollar, Gold," 1968 January 19. Speech, Industrie- und Handelskammer Stuttgart, Stuttgart, Germany. Holograph (Folder 22)
  - "Positive and Normative Economics: History and Analysis of the Ideas," 1968 February 9. Paper, Adolph Lowe Symposium on the Theory and Practice of Political Economics, New School for Social Research, New York City
    - General. Includes papers by others (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Research material and notes (Folder 2-4)
    - Holograph (Folder 5)
    - Typescript (Folder 6-9)
    - Correspondence with Melvin L. Greenhut and Robert L. Heilbroner (Folder 10)
  - Statement re The 1968 Economic Report of the President, United States Congress, Joint Economic Committee, 1968 February 19. Typescript and printed copy (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - "Current Policy Regarding the Balance of Payments," 1968 April 25. Statement, Board of Governors, Federal Reserve System. Typescript (Folder 2)
  - "Was heisst Entthronung des Goldes? Die Demonetisierung ist weit fortgeschritten," Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1968 July 20. Typescript (Folder 3)
  - "International Monetary Arrangements: Weighing Priorities and Alternatives," Financial Analysts Journal, 1968 July-August. Printed copy (Folder 4)
  - "Ist der Dollarkurs zu hoch?" Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1968 August 21. Printed copy (Folder 5)
  - "The Price of Gold," The Banker, 1968 September. Printed copy (Folder 6)
  - "The Transfer Gap of the United States," Banca Nazionale del Lavoro Quarterly Review, 1968 September. Printed copy (Folder 7)
  - Statement on the next steps in international monetary reform, United States Congress, Joint Economic Committee, Subcommittee on International Exchange and Payments, 1968 September 9. Printed copy (Folder 8)
  - "Education and Economic Growth," 1969. Speech, Centennial Celebration, University of Nebraska, Lincoln
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Reprint of first chapter of printed copy (Folder 10)
    - Reviews (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with University of Nebraska Press and New York University Press, 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Japanese translation. Typewritten preface (Folder 13)
  - Roads to Freedom: Essays in Honour of Friedrich A. von Hayek (with Erich Streissler et al.), Erich Streissler, Gottfried Haberler, Friedrich A. Lutz, and Fritz Machlup, eds., 1969. Printed copy of Fritz Machlup's contribution, "Liberalism and the Choice of Freedoms" (Folder 14)
  - "Wahrheiten uber das Wahrungssystem," Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1969 February 14. Typescript and printed copy (Folder 15)
  - Notes on flexible exchange rates, Claremont, California, 1969 March 8. Holograph (Folder 16)
  - Speech, Center for Public and Business Administration Education, National Chengchi University, Taipei, Taiwan, 1969 April. Correspondence with Chuan-ting Lu, 1970 (Folder 17)
  - "Speculations on Gold Speculation," American Economic Review, 1969 May. Printed copy (Folder 18)
  - "The Forward-Exchange Market: Misunderstanding between Practitioners and Economists," 1969 July? Typescript (Folder 19)
  - Citation on the occasion of the election of Ludwig von Mises as a Distinguished Fellow of the American Economic Association, in American Economic Review, 1969 September. Typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, including with James Tobin (Folder 20)
  - Comments on Milton Friedman, "The International Monetary System on the Eve of SDRs," Mont Pelerin Society, Caracas, Venezuela, 1969 September 7-13. Holograph (Folder 21)
  - Statement on the proposed IMF quota increase and its implications for the two-tier gold market, United States Congress, Joint Economic Committee, Subcommittee on International Exchange and Payments, 1969 November 13-14. Printed copy (Folder 22)
  - "Floating Rates, Greater Flexibility," ca. 1970. Conference paper or discussion of Jacques Rueff and Sir Leslie O'Brien. Notes (Folder 23)
  - Approaches to Greater Flexibility of Exchange Rates: The Burgenstock Papers (with C. Fred Bergsten, George N. Halm, Robert V. Roosa et al.), 1970.
    See also CORRESPONDENCE, George N. Halm
    - General (Folder 24)
    - Typescript and printed copy of Fritz Machlup's comments on Mr. Batt's paper (Folder 25)
    - Reviews (Folder 26)
  - "A Few Important Dates in the Last 25 Years of International Monetary Developments," 1970. Typescript (Folder 27)
  - Participation, Conference on International Mobility and Movement of Capital, Universities-National Bureau Committee for Economic Research, Brookings Institution, Washington, D.C., 1970 February 1
    - General. Includes notes (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Typescript of introduction to and review of proceedings (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Folder 3-6)
  - "On Terms, Concepts, Theories, and Strategies in the Discussion of Greater Flexibility of Exchange Rates," Banca Nazionale del Lavoro Quarterly Review, 1970 March. Reviews (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Participation in symposium and seminar on the knowledge industry, Research Institute of Telecommunications and Economics, Tokyo, Japan, 1970 June. Typewritten preface for printed copy (Chishiki Sangyo no Kozo) (Folder 2)
  - "Major Types of Modern Economics," 1970 June 24. Holograph (Folder 3)
  - "Trade Unions and Wages," 1970 July 30. Notes (Folder 4)
  - "Euro-Dollar Creation: A Mystery Story," Banca Nazionale del Lavoro Quarterly Review, 1970 September
    - Typescript and printed copy (Folder 5)
    - Comments from and correspondence with Stanley W. Black, Benjamin Jerry Cohen, Erik Dahmin?, Arthur B. Hersey, Fred H. Klopstock, Burton G. Malkiel, Helmut W. Mayer, Alexander K. Swoboda (Folder 6)
    - Spanish translation. Reviews (Folder 7)
  - "The Exchange Value of the Australian Dollar" (with J. Ashley Broadley), 1970 September 3. Typewritten memorandum for Mr. Holmes. Includes table (Folder 8)
  - "Longer Education: Thinner, Broader, or Higher," 1970 October 31. Paper, Invitational Conference on Testing Problems, Educational Testing Service, New York City
    - Correspondence with Marvin Bressler and David Riesman (Folder 9)
    - Notes, typewritten transcript of oral presentation, and printed copy of article based on the paper, "Are We Overselling College?" Princeton Alumni Week, 1971 October 12. Includes comments from Laurence Fenninger, Jr. and A. Sonnenfeld (Folder 10)
  - "Jacob Viner, 1892-1970" (with William J. Baumol and William S. Dix), 1970 November 9. Typescript (Folder 11)
  - "'Higher' Education Is Not for Everyone, Says Princeton's Machlup," The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1970 November 16. Printed copy, correspondence, and comments (Folder 12)
  - "Academic Freedom," Encyclopedia of Education, 1971. Typewritten excerpts, comments by Louis Joughlin, and correspondence (Folder 13)
  - Gendai Keizaigaku no Tembo (Views on Selected Topics in Modern Economics), 1971. Letter from Takuo Koide (Nihon Keizai Shimbun Sha Ltd.) (Folder 14)
  - "Notes to My Fellow Writers and Editors," 1971. Typescript (Folder 15)
  - "College Has Been Oversold," The Washington Post, 1971 February 28. Printed copy and reader's comments (Folder 16)
  - "World Inflation," 1971 March 26. Conference paper, Les Politiques de Stabilisation dans des Economies Interdependantes, Universite Paris-IX Dauphine, Paris, France. Typescript and printed copy. Includes holograph of discussion of Ronald I. McKinnon's paper (Folder 17)
  - "The Magicians and Their Rabbits," The Morgan Guaranty Survey, 1971 May. Comments (Folder 18)
  - "Changes in the International Monetary System and the Effects on Banks," 1971 May 25. Speech, 24th International Banking Summer School, Associazione Bancaria Italiana, Rome, Italy. Printed copy of Italian translation and correspondence with Gian Franco Calabresi (Folder 19)
  - Remarks on Terence W. Hutchison's paper, Vienna, Austria, 1971 June 19. Typescript (Folder 20)
  - "Higher Education: Too High for Too Many," Milwaukee Journal, Insight, 1971 June 27. Printed copy (Folder 21)
  - Discussion of Keniston and Gerzon, "Human and Social Benefits of Higher Education," ACE meeting, 1971 October. Typescript and correspondence with W. Lee Hansen (Folder 22)
  - The Book Value of Monetary Gold, 1971 December. Reviews and printed copy (Folder 23)
  - "Flexibility versus Fixed Exchange Rates," New York Times, 1971 December 26. Printed copy (Folder 24)
  - Discussion of J. O. N. Perkins, "Some Balance of Payments Effects of International Capital Flows with Special Reference to the Countries of the Pacific Area," 1972? Conference, Australian National University, Canberra, Australia. Holograph (Folder 25)
  - The Alignment of Foreign Exchange Rates, 1972
    - Reviews (Folder 26)
    - Correspondence with New York University Press (Folder 27)
  - "Chishiko Sangyo" (Knowledge industry), Gendai SeKai Hyakka Dai Ji Ten (Modern World Encyclopedia), 1972
    - Typescript
      - 1972 ("Knowledge Industry and Knowledge Work") (Folder 28)
      - 1982 ("Knowledge Industries and Knowledge Occupations"). Includes research material (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Kodansha Ltd., 1970; Information and Change, 1971-1972; and International Encyclopedia of Education (Barbara Barrett, George Psacharopoulos), 1981-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Foreword to the German Council of Economic Experts, Toward a New Basis for International Monetary Policy, 1972. Printed copy (Folder 3)
  - "Universal Bogey," in Maurice Peston and Bernard Corry, eds., Essays in Honour of Lord Robbins, 1972. Comment from Robert H. Strotz (Folder 4)
  - "The Expanded Role of SDRs and the Possibilities of an SDR Standard," 1972 January 14. Speech, Geneva, Switzerland. Typescript (Folder 5)
  - "Grundsatze fur ein besseres internationales Wahrungssystem," 1972 January 24. Speech, Stuttgart, Germany. Notes and typescript (Folder 6)
  - "What the World Thought of Jacob Viner," Journal of Political Economy, 1972 January-February. Typescript (Folder 7)
  - "What Was Left on Viner's Desk," Journal of Political Economy, 1972 March-April
    - Research material, including bibliographical and biographical information on Jacob Viner (Folder 8)
    - Notes and typescript (Folder 9)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1970-1975 (Folder 10)
      - Journal of Political Economy, 1970-1971 (Folder 11)
      - Winch, Donald. Includes his report on Jacob Viner's papers (Folder 12)
  - Discussion of the paper by H. Uzawa, Conference on the Management of Water Quality and the Environment, International Economic Association, Lyngby, Denmark, 1972 June 20
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Notes and typescript (Folder 14)
  - "The Dollar Fix, the Dollar Flex, and the Gold Boom," 1973. Typescript (in part holograph) (Folder 15)
  - "Learning More about Knowledge," Seventh Annual Report, National Endowment for the Humanities, 1973. Printed copy (Folder 16)
  - "Hochschulbildung fur jedermann: Eine Auseinandersetzung mit einem Gleichheitsideal," 1973 January 18. Speech, Universitat Basel, Basle, Switzerland. Typescript, English translation, and printed copy of expanded version (Folder 17)
  - "Less Rigidity Is not Enough," Euromoney, 1973 March. Printed copy (Folder 18)
  - "Ein einig Volk von Hochschulabsolventen?" Die Presse (Vienna), 1973 September 29/30. Printed copy (Folder 19)
  - "Der Aussenwert des Dollars: Zum Problem der Unterbewertung und Uberbewertung einer Wahrung auf den Devisenmarkten," 1974 January 15. Speech, Institut fur Weltwirtschaft an der Universitat Kiel, Kiel, Germany. Typescript, printed copy, and correspondence with Hubertus Muller-Groeling (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - "Wahrungspolitik und Zahlungsbilanz heute," 1974 January 23. Speech, Volkswirtschaftliche Gesellschaft des Kantons Bern, Bern, Switzerland. Clipping and letter from James Keogh (United States Information Agency) (Folder 2)
  - "An Analysis of the World-Wide Inflationary Situation," 1974 February 5. Paper, Management Symposium Davos, Davos, Switzerland. Holograph and typewritten notes (Folder 3)
  - "Recent Experiences with Floating Currencies," 1974 March 28. Panel presentation, Third Paris-Dauphine Conference on Money and International Monetary Problems, Recent Issues in International Monetary Economics, Paris, France. Typescript. (Folder 4)
    See also CORRESPONDENCE, Emil Maria Claassen
  - Discussion of Michael Bruno, "Efficiency and Equity in Public Education Expenditures," Conference on the Economics of Public Service, International Economic Association, Turin, Italy, 1974 April 2
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Holograph and typescript (Folder 6)
    - Printed copy of summary and correspondence (Folder 7)
  - "Vorkampfer einer liberalen Welt: Zum 75. Geburtstag des Nationalokonomen und Zeitkritikers Friedrich von Hayek," Die Presse (Vienna), 1974 May 8. Printed copy (Folder 8)
  - "Integrationshemmende Integrationspolitik," 1974 June 16. Speech, Institut fur Weltwirtschaft an der Universitat Kiel, Kiel, Germany. Proofs, printed copy of expanded version, and correspondence with Hubertus Muller-Groeling (Folder 9)
  - "Proxies and Dummies," Journal of Political Economy, 1974 July-August. Typescript (Folder 10)
  - "The History of Thought on Economic Integration," 1974 August 19. Presidential address, Fourth World Congress of the International Economic Association, Budapest, Hungary
    - Conference version
      - Correspondence with Tamas Foldi. Includes his introduction of Fritz Machlup, "Portraits of Economists" (Folder 11)
      - Proceedings published as Economic Integration: Worldwide, Regional, Sectoral, Fritz Machlup, ed., 1976. Reviews (Folder 12)
    - Vastly expanded version for publication of a book, History of Thought on Economic Integration, 1977.
      See also CORRESPONDENCE, Macmillan Press
      - Research material. Includes notes and correspondence (Folder 13-14)
      - Bibliographical references not cited (Folder 15)
      - Notes (Folder 16)
      - Typescript. Includes version distributed in February 1975 as "work in progress" (Folder 17)
      - Reviews (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Folder 2)
  - Speech on the gold standard, 1974 October. Holograph (Folder 3)
  - "Die 'heimliche' Steuer: Inflation," Kronenzeitung (Vienna), 1974 October 26. Printed copy (Folder 4)
  - "Friedrich von Hayek's Contribution to Economics," Swedish Journal of Economics, 1974 December
    - Research material. Includes bibliographies and reviews of Hayek's works (Folder 5)
    - Typescript (Folder 6)
    - Proofs and printed copy (Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Folder 8)
    - German translation (Wurdigung der Werke von Friedrich A. von Hayek). Notes, typewritten preface, printed copy, reviews, and correspondence with Georg Siebeck (J.C.B. Mohr/Paul Siebeck) and Alfred Bosch (Walter Eucken Institut) (Folder 9)
  - "Oil Imports: Disentangling the Issues," 1974 December 12. Conference paper. Typewritten notes (Folder 10)
  - "Reminiscences without Regrets," 1974 December 30. Paper, American Economic Association, San Francisco, California. Notes, typescript, and correspondence (Folder 11)
  - "The American Connection," 1975
    - Notes (Folder 12)
    - Typescript (Folder 13)
  - "Effects of Innovation on the Demand for and Earnings of Productive Factors" (with George C. Bitros and Kenneth W. Leeson), in H. R. Clauser, ed., Progress in Assessing Technological Innovation: 1974, 1975
    - General (Folder 14)
    - Research proposal (Folder 15)
    - Progress reports (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence
      - Kagann, Stephen E. (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - National Science Foundation (Folder 2)
      - New York University. Includes financial statements (Folder 3)
  - International Monetary Systems, 1975. Printed copy of partial German translation in Zukunft, 1977 September (Folder 4)
  - Preface and "Congress in Budapest (1974)," in The International Economic Association after 25 Years and Three Years Report 1971-1974, 1975. Printed copy (Folder 5)
  - "Workers Who Produce Knowledge: A Steady Growth, 1900-1970" (with Trude Kronwinkler), Weltwirtschaftliches Archiv, 1975
    - Typescript and printed copy (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, including with Rene L. Frey (Kyklos) and Hubertus Muller-Groeling (Folder 7)
    - Japanese translation. Printed copy (Folder 8)
  - Participation in seminar (with Mr. de Lattre and Mr. Casanova), Institut d'Etudes Politiques de Paris, Paris, France, 1975 January 16. Correspondence (Folder 9)
  - "Will There Be Another Great Depression?" 1975 January 20. Speech, Paris, France. Notes and holograph (Folder 10)
  - "On Myrdal and Hayek," Challenge, 1975 March/April. Letter to the editor. Printed copy (Folder 11)
  - "Problems of the International Monetary System," 1975 June 3. Speech, Banco de Vizcaya, Madrid, Spain. Typewritten outline and correspondence (Folder 12)
  - "Inflation und Rezession in der westlichen Welt," 1975 June 12. Speech, Gesellschaft fur Auslandskunde, Munich, Germany. Typescript and correspondence (Folder 13)
  - "Friedrich A. Hayek and His Early Work in Technical Economics," 1975 August 25. Speech, Mont Pelerin Society, Hillsdale, Michigan. Notes (Folder 14)
  - Discussion of the papers by Michael Parkin and Alexander K. Swoboda, Robert J. Gordon, Hans Genberg and Alexander K. Swoboda, Helmut Frisch, and J. Marcus Fleming, Conference on Inflation Theory and Anti-Inflation Policy, International Economic Association, Saltsjobaden, Sweden, 1975 August 28
    - General (Folder 15)
    - Notes (Folder 16)
    - Typescript (Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (Folder 18)
  - "Monetary Reform Is Back at Square One," New York Times, 1975 September 14. Typescript (Folder 19)
  - "They Don't Know They Are Sick," Publishers Weekly, 1975 September 29. Printed copy (Folder 20)
  - Statement on the IMF Gold Agreement, United States Congress, Joint Economic Committee, Subcommittee on International Economics, 1975 October 10. Press release, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence with John R. Stark (Folder 21)
  - "Publication and Other Forms of Information Services: The Problem of Forecasting Future Requirements and Performance," 1975 October 20. Paper, US/USSR Symposium, Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut. Notes, holograph, and typewritten abstract (Folder 22)
  - "The Economic Strangulation of the Science-Information Enterprise," 1975 December 30. Paper, American Economic Association, Dallas, Texas. Typescript (Folder 23)
  - Essays on Hayek (with William F. Buckley, Jr. and five others), Fritz Machlup, ed., 1976
    - General (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Reviews (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with Don Lipsett and others (Folder 3-4)
  - Selected Economic Writings of Fritz Machlup, George C. Bitros, ed., 1976
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Typescript
      - Outline (Folder 6)
      - Preface by George C. Bitros. Includes correspondence (Folder 7)
      - Index (Folder 8)
    - Proofs (Folder 9-12)
    - Proofs (Box 111, Folder 1-6)
    - Reviews (Folder 7)
    - Correspondence
      - Bitros, George C. (Folder 8)
      - New York University Press (Folder 9)
  - "The Free Market for Ideas and the Economic Viability of the Publishing Industry," 1976 January 17. Speech?, Paris, France. Notes (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - "Will Gold Be Remonetized?" Boletin Internacional (Bilbao, Spain), 1976 March. Printed copy and correspondence with Francisco Prieto (Folder 2)
  - "Between Outline and Outcome the Reform War Lost," in Edward M. Bernstein et. al., Reflections on Jamaica, 1976 April. Printed copy (Folder 3)
  - "The Dismal Science and the Illth of Nations," Eastern Economic Journal, 1976 April. Typescript and printed copy (Folder 4)
  - "Proposing a Toast," 1976 April 3. Speech celebrating the 200th anniversary of Adam Smith, An Inquiry Into the Nature and Causes of the Wealth of Nations, Glasgow, Scotland
    - Research material and notes (Folder 5)
    - Typescript (Folder 6)
  - "Conceptual and Causal Relationships in the Theory of Economic Integration in the Twentieth Century," 1976 June 8-11. Paper, Nobel Symposium on the International Allocation of Economic Activity, Stockholm, Sweden
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Typescript (Folder 8)
    - Proceedings, including summary of discussion of the paper by Fritz Machlup (Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Per Magnus Wijkman (Folder 10)
  - "Our Libraries: Can We Measure Their Holdings and Acquisitions?" American Association of University Professors Bulletin, 1976 Autumn
    - Printed copy and comments (Folder 11)
    - Reply to David W. Heron ("My Short Shoelaces and the Shortage of Library Data," American Association of University Professors Bulletin, 1977 Autumn). Printed copy and correspondence with David W. Heron (Folder 12)
  - Participation, "Looking Toward the 21st Century," Tokyo Colloquium, Tokyo and Kyoto, Japan, 1976 September 24-28. Notes on floating exchange rates and the knowledge industry (Folder 13)
  - "Payments for Oil, International Liquidity and Real Investment" and "Trends in the World Economy," 1976 September 30 -October 1976. Papers, Conference on Business in the Pacific Basin, Manila, Philippines. Typescript (Folder 14)
  - "Fleming in the Bellagio Group," 1976 November 12. Speech, J. Marcus Fleming Memorial Conference on the New International Monetary System, International Monetary Fund, Washington, D.C. Typescript and printed copy (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - "Exchange Rates, Comparative Costs, and the Pattern of Trade" (with Jacob Dreyer), Rivista internazionale di scienze economiche e commerciali, 1976 December. Printed copy (Folder 2)
  - "Frederick Harris Harbison (1912-1976)," in American Philosophical Society Year Book 1976, 1977. Printed copy (Folder 3)
  - Discussion of the papers by Emil Maria Claassen and John Kenneth Galbraith, Symposium zum 50. jahrigen Bestand des Osterreichischen Instituts fur Wirtschaftsforschung, Vienna, Austria, 1977 January 14. Typescript, proofs, printed copy, and correspondence with Felix Butschek (Folder 4)
  - "Publishing Scholarly Books and Journals: Is It Economically Viable?" Journal of Political Economy, 1977 February. Typescript, printed copy, and correspondence with Sanford V. Berg, Harry G. Johnson, George J. Stigler (Folder 5)
  - Interview on the Austrian School conducted by Axel Leijonhufvud, 1977 March 16. Typescript (Folder 6)